Florence Rena Sabin Papers 1916-1973 Mss.B.Sa12
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence (Box 1-39)
  - Wolff, S B, 1924-25
  - Wolff-Alport Chemicla Corporation, 1932
  - Wolfson, Mast, 1931
  - Woman's Digest, 1936
  - Women in Science, n.d.
  - Women's Association (Misc.), 1925-39
  - Women's City Club of New York, 1934
  - Women's Hall of Fame, Incorporated, 1937
  - Women's International League, 1932
  - Women's Medical Association, 1922-34
  - Women's University Club, 1937
  - Woodall, Mrs. H S, 1931
  - Woodruff, C Eugene, 1933
  - Woodruff, Helen M, 1924
  - Woods, Alan C, 1944
  - Woolf, M S, 1923
  - Woollard, H H, 1927-33
  - Woolley, Helen T, 1926
  - Woolley, Mary E, 1928-38
  - Wolley, Paul, 1927
  - World Center for Women's Archives, Incorporated, 1935-40
  - Worthley, Katherine, 1935-36
  - Wright, Arthur W, 1929-36
  - Wright, Samson, 1928
  - Wrinch, Dorothy M, 1941
  - Yale News, 1929
  - Yana, A, 1927
  - Yates, John L, 1923-32
  - Yoffey, J M, 1932-38
  - Young, Dorothy, 1924
  - Youngman, Charles L, 1925
  - Yu Wang Fu Association, 1926-38
  - Z, 1939
  - Zerfas, L G, 1929-35
  - Zeyland, J, 1933
  - Zimmer, Julius, 1933
  - Zinnser, Hans, 1924, 1937
- Series II. Photographs (Box 40)
  - Photographs, n.d.
    Scope and Contents note
    The following inventory is only a partial listing of the contents.
    - Autographed Photograph of Carlos Chagas [?], 1919, June 15; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portrait of Carlos Chagas autographed to Florence Sabin; There is an inscription on the photograph which appears to be in Portuguese, as well as a date: "Baltimore, June [?], 15, [1]919."
    - Dr. N. M. Stevens, bust, profile, seated looking at microscope., 1909; 1.0 Photograph(s); Stevens looking to microscope, lab beakers in foreground.
    - E. B. Wilson, Edward Mussey Hartwell, and six other men, full length, formal, seated and standing., 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal group portrait of eight men, sitting and standing.
    - Florence Sabin Portrait Bust, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 portrait of Sabin in coat and glasses.
    - Florence Sabin Seated at Desk with Five Unidentified Men, n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group portrait with Sabin seated at desk and five men standing behind her.
    - Florence Sabin, bust, formal., n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 view portrait of Sabin with long necklace.
    - Florence Sabin, bust, formal., n. d.; 1.0 Photograph(s); Frontal portrait of Sabin in later years.
    - Florence Sabin, full length, informal, standing., 1.0 Photograph(s); Sabin standing out doors near a tree.
    - Florence Sabin, half length, formal, standing, 1932; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portrait of Sabin holding medal.
    - Florence Sabin, with two unidentified men, full length, informal, standing., 1.0 Photograph(s); Sabin and two men standing out doors near a tree.
    - H. J. Cooper and F. G. Novy, 1937, June 25; 1.0 Photograph(s); Profile of Novy holding beaker with Cooper pointing at beeker and smiling.
      General note
      Inscription on back of photograph: "Dr. H. J. Cooper, Director, Research Department, N. J. H.; Dr. F. G. Novy, Emeritus Professor of Bacteriology and Hygiene, and Dean of University of Michigan. June 25, 1937, N. J. H. A. A. A. S."
    - M. H. Soule, H. J. Cooper and F. G. Novy, 1937, June 25; 1.0 Photograph(s); 3/4 group portrait of Soule, Cooper and Novy standing, wearing suits.
      Inscription on back of photograph: "Dr. Malcolm H. Soule; Dr. H. J. Cooper; Dr. F. G. Novy. June 25, 1937, N. J. H. A. A. A. S."
    - Sabin, Levy, Burgess and Long, Full Length Group Portrait, 1937, June 24; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full lenght group formal portrait, subjects standing out of doors.
      Inscription on back of photograph: "Dr. Sabin, Dr. Levy, Mr. Burgess, Dr. Long. June 24, 1937, N. J. H., A. A. A. S."
    - Women scientists and educators at Barnard College, including Florence Sabin., 1929; 1.0 Photograph(s); Eleven women standing on steps outside of a building.
  - Printing plates, n.d.